

ARTUR JĘDRZEJCZAK FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

artur.jedrzejczak@gmail.com



+48 664 289 281



Poznan, Poland



github.com/aratur

EDUCATION

Poznań University of Economics Master's Degree, Information Systems [2004 - 2009]

CERTIFICATION

- · Oracle DB SQL Certified Expert
- Oracle Certified Associate, Java SE 8
 Programmer
- IBM Data Science Professional Certificate
- Professional Scrum Master (PSM I)

PROFILE SUMMARY

Developer with almost 15 years of experience working with different technologies (over 2 years frontend) looking for a role as a mid/senior developer. Motivated, with willingness to learn new technologies and skills. Good team worker. Open to a B2B or an employment contract, remote work. Due to personal reasons 4 days working week is preferred. Currently on a B2B contract, with a 30 days notice period.

SKILLS

Frontend: React, React Router, React Query, Redux, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS,

SASS, Jest, NodeJS

Databases: Oracle DB, MS SQL Server, MySQL, SQLite

Tools: Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, Jira, DevTools, Postman, JMeter

IDE: Visual Studio Code, Atom, IntelliJ

EXPERIENCE

07/2020 - PRESENT SENIOR DEVELOPER AT CAPCO POLAND SP. Z O.O.

Project: Back-office application for HSBC

Responsibilities: Development of a fronted, banking applications for back-office employees.

Technologies: React, Redux, JavaScript, TypeScript, SASS, CSS, HTML

EXPERIENCE

07/2020 - PRESENT PERSONAL FRONTED DEVELOPMENT MASTERY PATH

Project: Non-commercial projects done in a private time

Responsibilities: To practice my skills, I implemented some projects that are available on my

github account. They have live versions (links on github) so feel free to look through the code or see how it works. (work that I normally do is not publicly available). First two are from the time when I started working with React. Recent ones are based on web designs from <code>frontendmentor.io</code>, using ready designs allowed me to focus more on the implementation side of things.

Technologies: React, Redux, React Query, JavaScript, TypeScript, CSS, SASS, HTML

06/2017 - 07/2020 SENIOR DEVELOPER AT CAPCO POLAND SP. Z O.O.

Project: New internet banking for BNP Paribas Polska

Responsibilities: Building migration engines for Identity Management System and Payments

Implementation of micro-services in the area of system administration,

payments

Technologies: Oracle SQL, Java, Spring Boot, Hibernate, JMeter

11/2015 - 02/2017

CONSULTANT AT ACCENTURE SP. Z O.O.

Project: Building a new Digital Bank in France for La Banque Postale based on mBank.

Responsibilities Designing an architecture of payments and cards for the new bank using a fit-

gap approach.

Technologies: APIs, UML, software architecture

01/2015 - 07/2015

CONSULTANT AT ACCENTURE SP. Z O.O.

Project: Post-merger integration for mBank and BRE Bank

between SharePoint and MS Project to track live-progress and reporting.

Technologies: C#, MS SQL Server, MS Project, SharePoint

03/2013 - 12/2014

CONSULTANT AT ACCENTURE SP. Z O.O.

Project: Post-merger integration for Santander Bank Polska and Kredyt Bank

Responsibilities Implementation of Migration engine in Loans area including reconciliation.

Technologies: Ab Initio (ETL), MySQL

12/2010 - 11/2013

ANALYST AT ACCENTURE SP. Z O.O.

Project: Post-merger integration for Santander Bank Polska

Responsibilities Implementation of Migration engine in Loans area including reconciliation.

Technologies: Ab Initio (ETL), MySQL

08/2008 - 11/2010

DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST AT BZ WBK S.A.

Project: Transfer Agent implementation for Arka Investment Funds

Responsibilities Implementation of reconciliation reporting, and business reporting

Technologies: Oracle, Business Objects

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych w zakresie przyszłych procesów rekrutacyjnych.